# **BRETT ITSUKI**

# Senior Full Stack Developer

## **SUMMARY**

I am a senior web developer who specializes in SPA development using JavaScript. I'm especially expertized in React.js and Vue.js as well as having some experience with Angular. I also have rich experience in building backend APIs using Node.js and Python. I love learning and challenging.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Full Stack Developer

07/2022 - Ongoing

- Learning & Practicing & Freelancing & Teaching
- More importantly SEEKING NEW CHALLENGE

#### Senior Frontend Developer

05/2020 - 07/2022

#### **Immersion**

Remote

- Developed many reusable components in React.js
- Implemented optimization for high performance
- Unit and E2E tests using Jest and Cypress
- Developed frontend using SCSS and jQuery

# Senior Full Stack Developer

11/2018 - 02/2020

NetCall

Remote

- Developed customer service platforms using React.js and Typescript
- · Created reusable codes and styles
- Developed frontend pages using Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS
- Developed back-end APIs using Express and Django and integrated third-party APIs

# Senior Frontend Developer

02/2018 - 08/2018

#### Itway

Remote

- Developed frontend using Material UI and React-Bootstrap
- · Worked with Figma designs
- Developed many mobile apps using React Native
- Took part in developing projects using Next.js and Rest APIs

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science**

2013 - 2017

# Singapore University of Technology and Design

## **SKILLS**

HTML / CSS ·

JavaScript / Typescript ·

React.js / Next.js · Angular ·

Vue.js / Nuxt.js · PHP / Laravel ·

Python / Django · Node.js / Express ·

MongoDB / PostgreSQL / MySQL ·

GraphQL / Apollo · AWS · Svelte ·

Git · Jira · Slack · Discord

# **LANGUAGES**

English	Proficient
Japanese	Intermediate

## **HOBBIES**

- Playing Football
- This is the state of the state
- Watching Movies
- Tistening to Music